Soviet Union and Russia Orthodox Subject Files, Inclusive: 1922 — 2018, undated, Bulk: 1970-1992
Baylor University, The Keston Center for Religion, Politics, and Society
- Samizdat, 1914-2008, undated; 2
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Men', Fr. Aleksandr. Works About (2 of 7), 1991 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Men', Fr. Aleksandr. Works About (3 of 7), 1992 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Men', Fr. Aleksandr. Works About (4 of 7), 1992 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Men', Fr. Aleksandr. Works About (5 of 7), 1992 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Men', Fr. Aleksandr. Works About (6 of 7), 1995 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Men', Fr. Aleksandr. Works About (7 of 7), 1993-1995, 2004, 2008, undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Men', Fr. Aleksandr. Interviews, Sermons, Writings (1 of 2), 1990, undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Men', Fr. Aleksandr. Interviews, Sermons, Writings (2 of 2), undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Men', Fr. Aleksandr. Obituaries, 1990 September (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Men', Fr. Aleksandr. Unsolved Murder, 1990-1995 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Men', Fr. Aleksandr. Commemoration, 1992-2000, undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Abbot Nikon, 1950-1951 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Pavlin, Archbishop of Mogilev, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Pivovarov, Fr. Aleksandr, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Romaniuk, Fr. Vasilii. Appeals (1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Romaniuk, Fr. Vasilii. Appeals (2 of 2), 1977-1979, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Romaniuk, Fr. Vasilii. Letters in Support Of, 1975-1978 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Rusak, Fr. Vladimir, 1983-1987 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Shpiller, Fr. Vsevolod (1 of 4), 1964 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Shpiller, Fr. Vsevolod (2 of 4), 1964-1965 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Shpiller, Fr. Vsevolod (3 of 4), 1966-1968 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Shpiller, Fr. Vsevolod (4 of 4), 1971-1974, 2008 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Elder Tavrion (Batozskii), 1976-1978 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (1 of 19), 1965 November (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (2 of 19), 1965 December (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (3 of 19), 1965 December (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (4 of 19), 1966 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (5 of 19), 1971-1974 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (6 of 19), 1975 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (7 of 19), 1976 January-March (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (8 of 19), 1976 April-December (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (9 of 19), 1977 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (10 of 19), 1978 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (11 of 19), 1979 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb. (12 of 19), 1979-1981 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb. (13 of 19), 1980 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (14 of 19), 1981-1982 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (15 of 19), 1987-1988 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (16 of 19), 1992 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (17 of 19), 1994 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb (18 of 19), 1995 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Yakunin, Fr. Gleb. (19 of 19), 1987 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Zheludkov, Fr. Sergei, 1974, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Living and Working Conditions of Orthodox Clergy, 1981 June-July (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Criticism of Russian Orthodox Church Policies by Believers, 1972, 1978-1987 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Emigration on Religious Grounds, 1971, 1980-1981 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Contacts with Foreigners, Émigré, 1979-1980 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Publications. Mnogaia Leta No 1, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Publications. Mnogaia Leta No 2, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Publications. Moskovskii Sbornik, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Publications. Collection of Christian Texts "Nadezhda", 1977-1979, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Publications. Newspaper "In the Light of Transfiguration", 1978-1980 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Publications. Newspaper "In the Light of Transfiguration", 1980-1981 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Publications. Monthly Almanac of Orthodox Christians "Blagovest", 1989 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Publications. Arts Union Journal for Young Christians "Ch'i My?", 1989 September (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Manuscripts. (1 of 14), 1968 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Manuscripts. (2 of 14), 1978 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Manuscripts. (3 of 14), 1980, undated (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Manuscripts. (4 of 14), 1981 November (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Manuscripts (5 of 14), 1982 January (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Manuscripts (6 of 14), 1982 September 25-October 1 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Manuscripts (7 of 14), 1987 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Manuscripts (8 of 14), 1987 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Manuscripts (9 of 14), 1987 December 2-1988 January 2 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Manuscripts (10 of 14), 1988 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Manuscripts (11 of 14), undated (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Manuscripts (12 of 14), undated (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Manuscripts (13 of 14), undated (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Orthodox Samizdat Manuscripts (14 of 14), undated (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Orthodox Samizdat. Appeals of Orthodox Christians to Patriarch Pimen, 1985-1988 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Orthodox Samizdat. Materials from Pavel Protsenko about Bishop Varnava (Beliaev), 1987-1988 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Orthodox Samizdat. Appeals of Orthodox Christians to Christians of All Denominations, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Orthodox Samizdat. Texts for Publication in Western Press, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Orthodox Samizdat. Round Table Discussion about Situation with the Russian Orthodox Church in the Year of the Millennium Anniversary of Christianity in Russia, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Unofficial Ecumenical Contacts, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Theology. Philosophy. Education. Ethics, 1972, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Theology. Essays, 1979-1983, undated (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Religion and Science, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Readers Conference in Moscow, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Relations with the Roman Catholic Church, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Relations with the Pentecostal Church, 1980-1981 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Ecumenical Contacts with Denominations within the Soviet Union, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Religion and National Identity. General, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Mnogaia Leta. Vypusk Pervyi, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Mnogaia Leta. Vypusk Vtoroi, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Russkoe Delo, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Russkii Vopros, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Veche No 1, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Veche No 2, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Veche No 3, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Veche No 4, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Veche No 5, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Veche No 6, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Veche No 8, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Veche No 9, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Veche. General, 1974-1977, undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Vybor No 1, 1987 July-September (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Vybor No 2 (1 of 2), 1987 October-December (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Vybor No 2 (2 of 2), 1987 October-December (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Vybor No 3, 1988 January-March (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Vybor No 4, 1988 April-June (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Vybor No 5, 1988 July-September (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Vybor No 6, 1988 October-December (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Vybor No 8, 1989 April-June (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Zemlia No 1, 1974 August (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Zemlia No 2, 1974 November (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Religion and National Identity. Publications. Zemlia. General, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Architecture. Restoration, 1983-1985 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (1 of 28), 1914 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (2 of 28), 1920 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (3 of 28), 1931 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (4 of 28), c. 1937 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (5 of 28), 1938 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (6 of 28), c. 1954 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (7 of 28), c. 1956 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (8 of 28), 1957 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (9 of 28), 1962-1984 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (10 of 28), c. 1975 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (11 of 28), 1977 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (12 of 28), 1978 September (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (13 of 28), 1978-1979 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (14 of 28), 1981-1984 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (15 of 28), 1982 September-1983 May (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (16 of 28), 1984-1985 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (17 of 28), 1985-1986 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (18 of 28), 1985-1987 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (19 of 28), undated (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (20 of 28), undated (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (21 of 28), undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (22 of 28), undated (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (23 of 28), undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (24 of 28), undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (25 of 28), undated (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (26 of 28), undated (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (27 of 28), undated (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Russian Orthodox Church. Literature (28 of 28), undated (Box 56, Folder 8)